ACTWU's Research Department Company Records 5619/012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Raliegh Manufacturers, Inc., 1959-1987 (Box 11, Folder 87)
- Rallye S.A., 1989 (Box 11, Folder 88)
- Ramm Styles, Inc., 1968-1988 (Box 11, Folder 89)
- Random House, Inc., 1985-1989 (Box 11, Folder 90)
- Rasbro Plastics, Inc., 1990 (Box 11, Folder 91)
- Raster Graphics Co., 1990 (Box 11, Folder 92)
- Ratner Corp. (Financial and General), 1965-1987 (Box 11, Folder 93)
- Ratner Corp. (News clippings), 1964-1988 (Box 11, Folder 94)
- Raven Manufacturing, Inc., 1989 (Box 11, Folder 95)
- Raxon Fabrics Corp. Allentown, P.A., 1971-1991 (Box 11, Folder 96)
- Raymark Corp. (Financial and General) (Formerly: Raybestos Manhattan), 1968-1989 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Recoating Specialties/Milin Industries, Inc., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Recticel Foam Corp. (See:Foamex L.P.), 1988-1990 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Red Bank Distribution, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Redken Laboratories, Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Reeves-Curon, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Reidbord Brothers Co. Buckhannon, West VA, 1963-1988 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Reliable Knitting Works, Inc., 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Reliable Products, Inc., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Renaissance Manufacturing Co., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Ren-O-Fab, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Resistance Technology Inc., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Revere Sink Corp., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Rexworks, Inc., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Reyes Industries, Inc., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Rhone-Poulec, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Richtex Corp., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Ricoh Corp., 1987-1990 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Riegel Textile Corp., 1973-1990 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Risley-Leete Co., Inc., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Rittenhouse, Inc., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Roane Hosiery, Inc., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Rob Ran, Inc., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Rob-Roy Co., 1959-1987 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Robert, Samuel Inc., 1979-1987 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- A.H. Robins Co., 1983-1989 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Rock Bottom Stores, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Rockelman Appliance Service Co., Inc., 1977-1990 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Rockford Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1980-1989 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Rockland Industries, Inc., 1976-1990 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Rockmart Manufacturing, Inc., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Rohammer Corp., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Romar Emmanuel and Associates, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Rome Industries, Inc., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Rome Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1971-1987 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Roomaker Curtain Co., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Rooster, Inc., 1967-1989 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Roper Corp., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Rosato Clothing Manufacturers, Inc., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Rose Hills Memorial Park Association, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Rose, W., Inc., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- RosPatch Corp., 1972-1989 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Ross-Simmons of Warwick, Inc., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Royal Care, Inc., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Royal Creations, Inc., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Royal Manufacturing Co., 1968-1987 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Roytex, Inc., 1983-1987 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- M. Rubin and Sons, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Rudnick and Sons, Inc., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Rudd Manufacturing Co., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Gianfranco Ruffini Sportswear, Inc., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Rugged Wear Ltd., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Rundel Products, Inc., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- S and R Knitting Mills, Inc., 1986-1990 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- S B I Acquisition Corp., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 55)
- SSB Finishing Co., Inc., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 56)
- Sackville Mills Shelby, NC Wallingford, PA, 1970-1989 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- Saint Andre International, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 58)
- Saint Andre Spinning, Inc., 1982-1985 (Box 12, Folder 59)
- St. Matthews Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 60)
- St. Peter's Hospital, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 61)
- Sam Nassi Co., Inc., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 62)
- Samax Dress Co., Inc., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 63)
- D. Samet, Inc., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 64)
- San Antonio Shoe, Inc., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 65)
- Sanderson Industries, Inc., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 66)
- Sandina Enterprises, Inc., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 67)
- Saunders Brothers, Inc., 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 68)
- Scent Pak., Inc., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 69)
- Scharf and Breit, Inc., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 70)
- Schleicher and Schuell, Inc., 1985 (Box 12, Folder 71)
- Schick, Inc. (See Also: Reeves Brothers, Inc.), 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 72)
- Schneider Mills, 1978-1987 (Box 12, Folder 73)
- School House Candy Co., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 74)
- Schuylkill River Industries, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 75)
- Scott Co., Inc. (Affiliate Shelburne Shirt Co.) Anderson, SC, 1970-1989 (Box 12, Folder 76)
- Scottdel, Inc., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 77)
- Sea Ray Industries, Inc., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 78)
- Seagram Co., Ltd., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 79)
- Sealy Holdings, Inc. Ohio Mattress Co. (Annual Reports, 1982-1987), 1983-1986 (Box 12, Folder 80)
- Seamco, Inc., 1978-1989 (Box 12, Folder 81)
- Sebaali, Inc., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 82)
- Security Textile Corp., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 83)
- Segal, Henry Co., 1965-1988 (Box 12, Folder 84)
- Sellersville Manufacturing Co., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 85)
- Selma Apparel Corp., 1970-1988 (Box 12, Folder 86)
- Sentinel Consumer Products, Inc., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 87)
- Serio Designs Ltd., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 88)
- Servend International, Inc., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 89)
- Service Center, Inc., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 90)
- Servisco (Financial and General), 1966-1986 (Box 12, Folder 91)
- Setex, Inc., 1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Sewell, Warren Clothing Co., 1978-1988 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Serio Designs Ltd., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Shanhouse Outerwear (Division of Wingspread Corp.), 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Sharper Image, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Shawmut Mills, 1986-1990 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Shelburne Shirt Co., Inc. (See also: Fall River Shirt Co.), 1950-1990 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Sheller-Globe Corp. (See Also: United Technologies), 1965-1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Shenandoanh Industries, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Sheplers Enterprises, Inc., 1990 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Sherri Lynn, Inc., 1981-1987 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Sherwood 2000, Inc., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Shipton Sportswear, 1982-1986 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Shockey Industries, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Shuford Mills, Inc., 1974-1983 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Siebe PLC, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Siegel-Robert, Inc., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Sigallo Ltd., 1972-1987 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Signal Plastics, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Silcofab Ltd. Guelph, Ontario, Canada, 1979-1985 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Silgan Pet Corp. (Cross Reference: Silgan Corp.), 1989 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Simpsonville Mills, Inc., 1980-1988 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Singer, R.J., 1986 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Sirena, Inc., 1986 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Sleep Products, Inc., 1990 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Sloan's Supermarkets, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Smith and Nephew, Inc., 1985-1990 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- W.H. Smith Wholesale Co., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Snugli. Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Solartex International, Inc., 1990 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Sonetronics, Inc., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Somerset Knitting Mills, Inc., 1968-1988 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Somerset Rural Electric Cooperative, Inc., 1988 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Soreltex International Inc., 1990 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Soundings Publications, Inc., 1988 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- South Boston Manufacturing, 1985-1987 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Southeast Muffler Co., Inc., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Southeastern Shirt Corp., 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Southern Apparel Contractors, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Southern Foundry Supply, Inc., 1988 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Southern Mills, Inc., 1982-1988 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Southern Plastics Co., Inc., 1987-1990 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Southern Wood Peidmont (ITT), 1989 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Southwestern/great American, Inc., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Spanco Industries, Inc., 1988 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Spectors Cleaners, Inc., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- Spencers, Inc., 1985-1989 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- Sponge, Inc., 1978-1990 (Box 13, Folder 48)
- Sports Belle, Inc., 1984-1989 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- Sportsotron, Inc., 1981-1987 (Box 13, Folder 50)
- Sportswear Corp. of America, Inc., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 51)
- Spunky Knits, Inc., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 52)
- Stanburg, Inc., 1972-1987 (Box 13, Folder 53)
- Standard Embossing Plate Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1984-1988 (Box 13, Folder 54)
- Standard Glove and Safety Equipment Co., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 55)
- Stanley Woolen Co. Inc., 1979-1989 (Box 13, Folder 56)
- Stanpat Products, Inc., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 57)
- Stanton Industries, Inc., 1990 (Box 13, Folder 58)
- Stanwood Mills, Inc. (Do not confuse with Stanwood Corp.), 1978-1988 (Box 13, Folder 59)
- Star Brite, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 60)
- Star Plastics, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 61)
- Star-Tex Corp., 1988 (Box 13, Folder 62)
- Starke Uniform Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1988 (Box 13, Folder 63)
- State Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1983-1987 (Box 13, Folder 64)
- State Street Boston Corp., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 65)
- State Wholesalers, Inc., 1988 (Box 13, Folder 66)
- Stearns Manufacturing Co., 1981-1990 (Box 13, Folder 67)
- Stedman Corp., 1962-1988 (Box 13, Folder 68)
- Steil, Inc., 1990 (Box 13, Folder 69)
- Steinhart Partners, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 70)
- Stern and Stern Textiles, Inc., 1966-1988 (Box 13, Folder 71)
- Sterling Drug Co., 1988 (Box 13, Folder 72)
- Sterling Dye Corp., 1984-1990 (Box 13, Folder 73)
- Sterling Last Corp., 1990 (Box 13, Folder 74)
- Douglas Stevens Plastics Inc., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 75)
- Steven's Sportswear Co., Inc., 1979-1989 (Box 13, Folder 76)
- Stillwater, Inc., 1951-1986 (Box 13, Folder 77)
- Stitches, Inc., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 78)
- Stone Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1962-1988 (Box 13, Folder 79)
- Stonhard Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 80)
- R.L. Stowe Mills, 1951-1989 (Box 13, Folder 81)
- Stowe-Woodward Co., 1967-1984 (Box 13, Folder 82)
- Strand Core, Inc., 1990 (Box 13, Folder 83)
- Strand Glove and Safety Equipment Co., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 84)
- Straus Knitting Mills, Inc., 1978-1990 (Box 13, Folder 85)
- Sulzle, B.G., Inc., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 86)
- Summergrade, N. and Sons (Summergrade Corp.), 1971-1987 (Box 13, Folder 87)
- Sumitomo Rubber Industries Ltd., 1985-1987 (Box 13, Folder 88)
- Summit Apparel Manufacturing Corp., 1988 (Box 13, Folder 89)
- Sunflag Group, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 90)
- Sun Ray, Inc., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 91)
- Sun Sportswear, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 92)
- Sunny Cha, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 93)
- Superior Bias Binding, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 94)
- Superior Pants Co., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 95)
- Superior Trim, Inc., 1978-1989 (Box 13, Folder 96)
- Supra Sports, Inc., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 97)
- Sutherland Lumber Co., 1990 (Box 13, Folder 98)
- Swafford Fay Originals, Inc., 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 99)
- Swarovski America Limited, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 100)
- Sweatt's, 1980-1988 (Box 13, Folder 101)
- Switlik Parachute Co., Inc., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 102)
- T F M Active Sportswear, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 103)
- T F M Industries, Inc., 1984-1990 (Box 13, Folder 104)
- T.G. Specialists, Inc., 1988 (Box 13, Folder 105)
- TLC Group, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 106)
- TPI Industries of Middletown, Inc. (Box 13, Folder 107)
- TS Trim Industries, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 108)
- Tanden, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 109)
- Tavern on the Green, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Taxi Drivers, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Tel Plus Communications, Inc., 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Tennessee Cotton Knits, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Tennessee Tape and label Corp., 1989 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Tennier Industries, 1982-1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Tensar Structures, Inc., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Termatec Molding, Inc., 1989 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Tetra Pak Rausing, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Textile Prints Corp., 1976-1988 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Textile Prints of Florida, Inc., 1985-1989 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Texture-Tex, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Texwipe Co., Inc., 1989 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- THAW Corp., 1989 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Theatrical Accessories, Inc., 1989 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Thomas Scientific, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Glen Thornhill Interests, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Tien Hu-Customer Tien Hu-Asian Production (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Tiro Industries, Inc., 1989 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Tobias Katzin Co., 1975-1988 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Toll-Gate Garment Co., Inc., 1967-1989 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Tonner, William T. Co., Inc., 1977-1985 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- TOPCO Custom Printed Sportswear, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Top Look Leather Fashions, Inc., 1985-1987 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Townhouse-Penthouse Industries, Inc. (Brittany Furniture, Division), 1990 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Tracey-Luckey Co., Inc., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Transit Plastic Extrusions, Inc., 1989 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Transportation General, Inc., 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Travers Tool Co., Inc., 1990 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Tri-Glass Industries, Inc., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Tri-State Glove, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Triangle Industries, Inc., 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Trident Tool Co., Inc., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Trico Products, Inc., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Tridon, Inc., 1988 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Trimfit, Inc., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Trimfoot Co., 1985-1987 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Triple Associates Ltd., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Triumph Pet Industries, Inc., 1989 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Troy Sunshade Corp., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Tuff Togs Industries, Inc., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Turbine Components Corp., 1990 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Tuscarora Yarns, Inc., 1973-1989 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- Twilight Color and Chemical Co, Inc., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Twin More Clothes, Inc., 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- UNR Industries, Inc., 1981-1990 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- USK, Inc., 1988 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- U.S. Button Corp., 1990 (Box 14, Folder 48)
- U.S. Chemical and Plastic, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 49)
- U.S. Sample Co., Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 50)
- U.S. Sports, Inc., 1981-1989 (Box 14, Folder 51)
- U.S. Thread, Inc., 1990 (Box 14, Folder 52)
- Uniform Cap Accessories, Inc., 1990 (Box 14, Folder 53)
- Uniform Ideas, Inc., 1983-1988 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Uniform Rental Service, Inc., 1988 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Unilever PLC, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 56)
- Union Camp Corp. (Financial and General), 1990 (Box 14, Folder 57)
- Union Thread, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 58)
- Uniroyal Goodrich Tire Co., 1988 (Box 14, Folder 59)
- United Distributors, Inc., 1989 (Box 14, Folder 60)
- United Foods, Inc., 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 61)
- United Piece Dye Works, Inc., 1970-1987 (Box 14, Folder 62)
- United Printing, Inc., 1990 (Box 14, Folder 63)
- United Research Laboratories, Inc., 1988 (Box 14, Folder 64)
- United Solid, Inc., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 65)
- Unitog Rental Services FOIA Requests, 1980-1988 (Box 14, Folder 66)
- Universal Fuller Co., Inc., 1990 (Box 14, Folder 67)
- Universal Furniture Industries, Inc., 1981-1989 (Box 14, Folder 68)
- Universal Textiles, Inc., 1985 (Box 14, Folder 69)
- Universal Trousers, Inc., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 70)
- Universal Uniforms, Inc., 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 71)
- Up North Plastics, Inc., 1988-1996 (Box 14, Folder 72)
- Utica Converters, Inc. (See Also: Dunlop Tire and Rubber), 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 73)
- Utica Duxbak Corp., 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 74)
- University Microfilms, Inc., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 75)
- V.I. Enterprises, Inc., 1988 (Box 14, Folder 76)
- Valleylab, Inc. (See Also: Pfizer), 1981-1987 (Box 14, Folder 77)
- Valdese Weavers, Inc., 1990 (Box 14, Folder 78)
- Vanco Industries, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 79)
- Velcro Industries, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 80)
- Velcro U.S.A., Inc., 1978-1987 (Box 14, Folder 81)
- Velvet Textile Co., Inc., 1972-1988 (Box 14, Folder 82)
- Venture Uniforms, Inc., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 83)
- Vermont Clothing, Inc., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 84)
- Vernon Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 85)
- Verosol USA, Inc., 1988 (Box 14, Folder 86)
- Versailles Formalwear, Inc., 1985-1997 (Box 14, Folder 87)
- Versatech Industries, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 88)
- Vickers Co. (Trinova Corp), 1989 (Box 14, Folder 89)
- Victor-Balata Belting Co., 1946-1988 (Box 14, Folder 90)
- Victory Cap Front Manufacturing, Inc., 1988 (Box 14, Folder 91)
- Viola Sportswear, Inc., 1973-1987 (Box 14, Folder 92)
- Viz Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 93)
- Volunteer Apparel, Inc., 1984-1988 (Box 14, Folder 94)
- Volunteer Leather Co., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 95)
- Wags Manufacturing, Inc., 1980-1987 (Box 14, Folder 96)
- B.B. Walker Co., 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 97)
- Wapakoneta Products Division, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Warner Woven Labels, Inc., 1980-1990 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Washington Apparel Group, Inc., 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Washington Industries, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Washington Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1965-1990 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Warren Swell Clothing Co. (Warren Swell Co.), 1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Wash Technologies, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Weatherbee Coats, Inc., 1968-1987 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Webster Brick Co., Inc., 1978-1988 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Weeks Textile Co., 1987 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Weihl and Tweel, 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Weintraub, George and Sons, Inc., 1982-1987 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Welch Apparel, Inc., 1989 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Wellington Industries, Inc., 1971-1987 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Wellington Manufacturing, Inc., 1989 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Wellmade Industries, Inc., 1988 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Wen-Su Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1985-1987 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Werthan Industries, Inc., 1974-1985 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Westark Garment Manufacturing, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Westbrook Spinning Co., Inc., 1981-1990 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Westbury Knitwear, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Western Art Manufacturing Co., 1987 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Western Industries, Inc., 1988 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Westminster Village, Inc., 1985-1990 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Westpoint Casket Co., Inc., 1987 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Westview Convalescent Center, Inc., 1990 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Westwood Lighting Group, Inc., 1985-1988 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Wex-Tex Industries, Inc., 1983-1987 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Weyerhaeuser Co., 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Weyerhaeuser Paper Co., 1989 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Whirlpool Corp., 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Whitestone Products, Inc., 1990 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- White Swan Uniforms, Inc., 1988 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- F. Whitney and Co., Ltd., 1987 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Whittle Communications, Inc., 1988 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Williams Food Service, Inc., 1989 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Willis and Geiger, Inc., 1978-1987 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Wilson Bottling Corp., 1987 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Wingspread Corp., 1978-1988 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Winsome Togs, Inc., 1973-1987 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Jack Winter Apparel, Inc., 1980-1989 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Winthrop-Atkins Co., Inc., 1987 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Wior Corp David Brown, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- Wire Belt Company of America, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Wiscassett Mills Co., 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Wise Co., Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 46)
- Woodland Manufacturing Corp., 1978-1988 (Box 15, Folder 47)
- Woods, Harvey Co., 1990 (Box 15, Folder 48)
- Worcester Co., Inc., 1987 (Box 15, Folder 49)
- Work Connection, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 50)
- Workers Owned Sewing Co., 1981-1986 (Box 15, Folder 51)
- Wrap Spun Yarns, Inc., 1988 (Box 15, Folder 52)
- Wright and Filippis, Inc., 1990 (Box 15, Folder 53)
- Wyoming Valley Garment Co., 1988 (Box 15, Folder 54)
- Yale-New Haven Hospital, Inc., 1990 (Box 15, Folder 55)
- Yalobusha General Hospital, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 56)
- Yankee Linen Supply, Inc., 1990 (Box 15, Folder 57)
- Yarn Industries, Inc., 1982-1989 (Box 15, Folder 58)
- ZRM Industries, Inc., 1980-1988 (Box 15, Folder 59)
- Zayre Corp., 1986 (Box 15, Folder 60)
- Zayre Corp., 1964-1987 (Box 15, Folder 61)
- Zenith Products Corp., 1988 (Box 15, Folder 62)
- Samuel Zimber and Son, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 63)
- S. Zimmerman Bias Binding Corp, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 64)
- A-1 Manufacturing Co. Correspondence, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- A-1 Manufacturing Co. D & B Reports, 1960-1963 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- A-1 Manufacturing Co. Financial, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- A.A. Processing, Brooklyn, NY, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- AAA Bag & Burlap Co., St. Louis, Missouri, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- AAA Tent & Awning Co., 1969 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- ABC Photo Gravure Supply Co., 1975 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- ABC School Uniforms, Inc., 1967 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- A.C.E. Engraving, Hawthorne, New Jersey, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- ACS Industries, Inc., Miami, Oklahoma, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- AGS Service Corp, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- A & K Corp., 1970-1973 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- AMF, Inc. Annual Reports, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- A P Parts Corp., 1967 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- A & P Wood Products, Yale, Michigan, 1964-1972 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- A.P.A. Screen Prints, Inc., Paterson, NJ, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- ATA Textiles, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- ATO Inc. (See Reference Sheet for folder identification), 1973-1976 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- A-V Product Co., 1968 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- A & W Products Co., Port Jervis, NY, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- AALFS Manufacturing Co., 1962-1967 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- I. Aaronson Ltd., 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Abate Clothing Company, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Abbeville Shirt Co., 1967 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Abbey-Lee Sportswear, 1969-1973 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Abbot Worsted Mills, Wilton, NH, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Morty Abels, Inc., 1965-1971 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- L. Abelson, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Aberle Hosiery Company, Columbia, Tennessee Financial, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Aberle Hosiery Company, Columbia, Tennessee Labor, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Aberle Industries, Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Abney Mills, Greenwood, SC (Panola Mills), 1971 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Abney Mills, Newry, SC (Courtney Manufacturing Co.), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Abuel Co., Kansas City, Mo., 1975 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Academic Press & Johnson Reprint, Spring Valley, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Acadia Company, Inc. Pa., 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Accent American, Ltd., 1975 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Accent of California, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Accubond Rebuilders, Inc., Buffalo, NY, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Accu-Screen, Inc, Babylon, L.I., NY, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- Ace Lace Corp., Brooklyn, NY, 1960-1971 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Ace Sportswear Company, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Ace Sweater Mills, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 43)
- Ace Work Glove Co., 1971 (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Ackerman Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 16, Folder 45)
- Simon Akerman Clothes (D&B Reports), 1963 (Box 16, Folder 46)
- Simon Akerman Clothes (News Clippings), 1957-1965 (Box 16, Folder 47)
- Ackley Uniform Co., 1962 (Box 16, Folder 48)
- Ackshand Knitting Co., 1965 (Box 16, Folder 49)
- Acme Engraving Co., Paterson, NJ, 1970-1976 (Box 16, Folder 50)
- Acme Knitting Goods Processing, Inc., Brooklyn, NY, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 51)
- Acme of California, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 52)
- Acorn Clothing Co., 1969 (Box 16, Folder 53)
- Acqua Brook Corp., 1968 (Box 16, Folder 54)
- Acritex Yarns, Ltd., Perth, Ontario, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 55)
- Acton Nipples, Inc., Acton Vale, Quebec (Subsidiary Canvil Ltd.), 1969-1975 (Box 16, Folder 56)
- Acton Shoe Co., Ltd., Acton Vale, Quebec (subs Lambert, Alfred Inc.?), 1971-1974 (Box 16, Folder 57)
- Acushnet Carpet Mills, New Bedford, MA, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 58)
- Acute Systems, Ltd. (d/b/a/ McDonalds), 1974 (Box 16, Folder 59)
- Adam Meldrum & Anderson, 1968-1973 (Box 16, Folder 60)